There's no one in the village...
村子里空无一人…
My goodness, Mr. Alvin is so unpopular.
天啊 埃尔文先生这么不受欢迎
No matter how unpopular I am, it won't make the whole village disappear.
再怎么不受欢迎 也不会让整村的人都不见
They should've run away because they knew you were coming.
应该是知道你要来 所以大家都逃走了吧
If they knew I'd come,
若知道我会来
they would line up to shake hands with me.
大家就会大排长龙地来跟我握手
Celia, it's all right.
希莉 没事的
The dwarfs will be rescued.
矮人们一定会得救的
The dwarfs don't get along well with us.
矮人族 跟我们不合的种族
Is there any misunderstanding between elves and dwarfs?
精灵族和矮人族之间 有什么误会吗
Yes, I failed to bargain in the dwarfs' clothing store before.
是的 以前曾在矮人族的服装店 砍价失败了
It's your personal problem! It has nothing to do with race!
这是你个人的问题 跟种族无关
I walked around. There's no one in the village.
我晃了一圈 村里都没人
Me too. It looks like they were taken away.
我也是 看来应该是被带走了
I see.
这样啊
Just in case, I'll see if the wounded are hiding.
为了以防万一 我找找看有没有躲起来的伤患
You can use that magic?
你能使用那种魔法哦
I'm a healer. I can find the weak.
我是僧侣 有找到虚弱之人的能力
You're a monster that targets the wounded.
根本就是以伤患为目标的怪物
Holy power.
神圣力量
Please save those who have been abandoned because of injury.
请拯救因受伤而被抛弃之人
Please show where the poor and weak are.
请指示可怜虚弱之人的所在之处
You look like a real healer.
看起来好像真的僧侣
How ugly.
好丑
Go and find it.
去寻找吧
If there's really a weak person, we have to help him.
如果真的有虚弱的人在 就得去帮助他才行
There's a response around here.
这附近有反应
And he's very weak!
而且非常的虚弱
What? Where is it?
什么 在哪
I'm not weak.
我不虚弱啊
I'm sorry. You're weak.
抱歉 你原本就很弱
But my body is strong!
但我的身体很健壮
But we can't save them if we don't know where they were taken.
可是 若不知道他们被带到哪 就无法救他们
-That's right. -Celia heard it!
-就是说啊 -希莉听到了
The bad people took everyone to the castle cell.
坏人把大家带到城堡牢房里
Right there!
就在那
It's like a bad person's favourite place.
真像坏人喜欢的地方
DON'T HURT ME, MY HEALER
(这个僧侣有够烦)
"THE TITLE" "FINALLY, IT COMES TO THE LAST EPISODE. THANK YOU FOR WATCHING TILL NOW. INCLUDING" I'm so worried.
(此次的标题 终于到了最后一集 感谢大家收看到现在) 我好担心哦
"THE STAFF OF THE ORIGINAL WEBSITE, WE'D LIKE TO EXPRESS OUR SINCERE THANKS TO YOU." I wonder if they're doing well.
(包括原著网页的工作人员们一同向大家献上诚挚地道谢) 不知道卡菈他们顺不顺利
"SINCE THERE'S NO FINAL ENDING IN THE ORIGINAL WORK, THIS EPISODE IS ALMOST ORIGINAL." Calm down.
(因为原著中尚未出现最后结局的内容 所以这集几乎是原创) 冷静点
"BUT THE CONTENT IS ALSO FROM THE ORIGINAL AUTHOR, TANNEN NI HAKKOU." Don't worry too much.
(但内容也是来自原著作者丹念发酵老师) 不用太担心
"THE LINES AND INSPIRATION OF DWARF CHARACTERS ARE DESIGNED TO INTEGRATE THE CONTENTS BEFORE AND AFTER." Nonsense.
(设计的矮人角色台词和灵感 努力把前后内容都统整起来) 说什么傻话
"FINALLY, WE CAN REST ASSURED. BUT IT'S LONELY TO END LIKE THIS. HOPEFULLY, CARLA AND ALVIN CAN CONTINUE TO" Sh.
(终于可以放心了 但就这样结束真令人感到寂寞) 嘘
"GET ALONG. AND THE ORIGINAL STORY ISN'T OVER YET. PLEASE CONTINUE TO SUPPORT IT." Celia finally fell asleep.
(希望卡菈和埃尔文能继续相处 而原著的故事还没结束 请务必继续支持) 希莉好不容易睡着了
"THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR WATCHING. THANKS AGAIN SINCERELY." He's a real villain.
(非常感谢大家的收看 再次献上真诚地感谢) 对方可是真正的坏蛋
"THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR EPISODE TWELVE, "FINAL EPISODE"." Dolman.
(真的非常谢谢大家的第十二话"最后一集") 多尔曼
Yes. I wonder if Carla's "communication skills" can come in handy.
是啊 不知大姐的"沟通能力" 能否派上用场
I know, right?
对吧
I hope they can come back soon safely.
希望能快点平安回来
Carla.
卡菈
What are you doing with the flowers?
你拿花干嘛
Camouflage.
伪装
It's too eye-catching. Put them down.
太显眼了 放下
Get down!
趴下
Brothers, how is it?
兄弟们 如何
Is anything unusual?
有无异常
He is...
他是…
The fugitive.
逃犯男
It's Brigan.
是布利迦
What a special posture of getting down.
趴下的姿势真特别
Who would come to such a place?
谁会来这种地方
Haven't the dwarfs revealed where the imperial body is?
矮人们 还没供出御神体在哪吗
Yes. We can't be rough with them.
是啊 又不能对他们动粗
They're first-rate craftsmen, after all.
毕竟他们是一流的工匠
We can only sell them at a high price if they're unharmed.
毫发无伤 才能卖到高价
So he's an accomplice of Dolman.
原来他是多尔曼的同伙
It seems so.
看样子没错
He ruins the reputation of adventurers.
真是个弄臭冒险家名声的家伙
-Reconnaissance over. -Thank you for your hard work.
-侦察结束 -辛苦了
On the left side of the castle, there's a cell that seems to be surrounded by a high wall.
在城堡左侧 有个疑似被高墙围绕的牢房
All right. Fortunately, tonight is the new moon.
好 好在今晚是新月
Let's sneak into it in the dark.
趁着黑夜混进去吧
Be quiet. No talking.
安安静静的 禁止谈话
What are you doing?
干嘛啦
Your body language is too annoying.
你的肢体语言太烦了
I suggest that Ryoko takes us in.
我提议 让灵子带我们进去
It's hard to understand.
超难懂
Can you really do it?
你真的能做到吗
I can put you in my body if there are only two people.
只有两人的话 我还能收纳进体内带进去
Put us in your clothes...
收纳进衣服…
We'll get in your bag.
进包包里吧
We're here.
到了
Be quiet. There are two demon soldiers guarding outside the wall.
安静 墙外有两位魔兵在看守
The cell has been cast with dark magic, so I can't get in.
这座牢房被施展了黑暗魔法 所以我进不去
Be careful, both of you.
两位请小心
I got it. Thank you.
知道了 谢谢
It looks like nobody is guarding.
好像没人看守
It's not even locked.
甚至没有上锁
Fortunately, Brigan is a lazy guy.
好在布利迦是个懒惰的家伙
Are you going to ask us again?
又来问我们了吗
No matter how many times you ask us, we won't tell you where the imperial body is.
不管问我们几次 我们都不会说出御神体在哪的
Be quiet. It'll be heard by the guards outside.
安静 会被门外看守人听到的
We are your companions.
我们是你们的同伴
That's right.
没错
I'm all-loving and kind...
我既博爱又慈爱…
I'm here to save the dwarfs I don't like.
来救不怎么喜欢的矮人族
Shut up. Things will get very troublesome.
闭嘴 事情会变得很麻烦
Is the village head here?
村长在吗
I'm the village head.
我是村长
"I'M THE VILLAGE HEAD OF THE DWARFS." I see.
(我是矮人村长) 原来如此
My granddaughter asked you to save us.
是我孙女拜托你们来救我们的
Thank you.
谢谢你们
She's hiding in a safe place.
她现在躲在安全的地方
Dolman's target seems to be the imperial body.
多尔曼的目标好像是御神体
The imperial body can dispel dark magic with holy power.
御神体能以神圣力量驱散黑暗魔法
Dolman fears that power.
多尔曼就是畏惧那股力量
This castle is a fortress built by our ancestors.
这座城堡是我们祖先建造的要塞
Although it has become a ruin,
虽然已经成为废墟
the imperial body is hidden deep in the castle.
但御神体就藏在这座城堡深处
I'll tell you where it is.
我告诉你们在哪
Would you like to help us take down Dolman and get us out?
你们愿意帮我们打倒多尔曼 救我们出去吗
What's wrong?
怎么了
When you're asking for help,
有求于人的时候
shouldn't you kneel and kowtow...
跪下来磕头不是基本…
Get the timing of speaking right!
搞清楚说话的时机
We kneel and kowtow.
我们跪下磕头
Please help us.
拜托你们了
It took a lot of time to collect the items. But we finally got in.
为了收集道具花了不少时间 但总算进来了
How soon we come to a fork. Are we going straight?
这么快就遇到岔路 要直走吗
Yes. There's a trap if we're going straight...
是的 直走有陷阱…
Then don't say "yes".
那就别说"是的"啊
I'll pay attention to it next time.
我下次注意
It's a dead end.
没路了
The maze is very complicated. Could it be the wrong way?
这个迷宫很复杂 会不会是走错了
We followed the map drawn by the village head. It won't go wrong.
我们照着村长画的地图走 不会错的
After pressing the slate of the triangle symbol...
按下三角符号的石板后…
I see. There are hidden channels.
原来如此 有隐藏通道
No. There will be a trap.
不 会出现陷阱
Sorry to trouble you again.
抱歉 又麻烦你了
Please say that earlier.
拜托你早点说
I'll pay attention to it next time.
我下次注意
The imperial body should be in this room.
御神体应该在这个房间里
Have you asked how to open the door?
你问过打开门的方式了吧
Yes.
问了
Turn the stone statue on the right 90 degrees to the left.
把右边的石像往左转90度
All right. After turning... Will there be a trap?
好 转了后…会出现陷阱吗
Yes, it's a complete trap.
是的 很完整的陷阱
Nonsense!
是个屁啦
Don't you want to improve your unique skill?
你不是要精进你的拿手绝技吗吗
I don't recall I have such a unique skill.
我不记得我有这项绝技
Every time I have to bother Ryoko to save me.
每次都还要麻烦灵子来救我
Hurry up and tell me the right order to open the door!
快告诉我正确的开门顺序
How boring.
真无聊
The dwarfs' skill is amazing.
矮人的技术真令人惊艳
Awesome.
太厉害了
Women's underwear made by dwarfs is also great.
矮人做的女性内衣也很棒哦
Don't compare this to underwear.
别把这个跟内衣相提并论
That's the imperial body, right?
那就是御神体吧
It seems so.
好像是
There should be no traps.
应该没有陷阱
But just in case you stay here.
但以防万一 你留在这
Okay.
好
It's different from what I thought.
跟我想像的不太一样
Thank you for leading the way.
感谢你们带路
What?
什么
Lord Dolman has seen it through.
多尔曼大人早就看透了
Brigan! And that guy...
布利迦 还有那家伙…
It's Dolman, the Dark Wizard.
是黑暗大魔导士 多尔曼
I sensed the power of the dark elf, so I came to have a look.
我感觉到黑暗精灵的力量 所以来一探究竟
I didn't expect to hit the jackpot.
没想到还中了大奖
It means you sensed my charm.
意思是说 你感觉到我的魅力咯
-It's magic. -I didn't sense your charm.
-是魔力 -没感觉到你的魅力
All right. Give me the crown.
好了 把王冠给我吧
You wish!
谁要给你啊
Hang on a second, Mr. Alvin.
埃尔文先生 请稍等
Just leave it to me.
这里就交给我吧
Since you're the villain boss, I have something to say.
既然你是坏蛋魔王角 那我就有话要说了
What is it?
说什么
If you would give us half the world, we can negotiate.
若你愿意分半个世界给我们 我们就有交涉的可能性
That's not what good people should say.
这不是好人该说的话
I'm sorry. I didn't intend to negotiate.
抱歉 我没打算交涉
But if you give me the crown, I can let you join my army as a soldier.
但如果乖乖把王冠交给我 我可以让你加入我的军团当小兵
And Alvin, I'll order you about.
然后埃尔文 我会好好使唤你的
No, I'll do it.
不 我来使唤就好
I refuse!
我都拒绝
Then...
那就…
Carla!
卡菈
Geez, let go of Carla!
可恶 放开卡菈
How? Would you give me the crown?
怎么样 愿意把王冠交给我了吗
Carla, are you all right?
卡菈 你没事吧
Miss Anna, thank you.
安娜小姐 谢谢你
I was so worried, so I came.
我太担心 所以就来了
Alvin, now!
埃尔文 趁现在
Okay. Imperial body, break the dark magic!
好 御神体 击破黑暗魔法吧
Idiot!
蠢货
Why?
为什么
Mr. Alvin!
埃尔文先生
Alvin!
埃尔文
Drop your weapon.
放下武器
If you don't want her face hurt, give me the crown.
如果不希望她的脸蛋受伤 就把王冠交出来
No way. Run away.
不行 快逃
Don't worry about me. Before the imperial body is robbed...
别管我 御神体还没被抢走前
But...
可是…
I still have the value of being a hostage, so don't worry.
我还有当人质的价值 所以别担心
And it's like the lines the protagonist would say. I've always wanted to say it.
而且这很像主角会说的台词 我一直都很想说说看
I got it...
我知道了…
Ryoko, let's run away.
灵子 快逃吧
Okay.
好
Don't you run away.
别想逃
Put that girl in the cell.
把那个丫头丢进牢里
Quick, find it. Get the crown back.
快找 把王冠抢回来
It's great, right? You have value.
很棒吧 你有利用价值了
The selling price of the dark elf is very high.
黑暗精灵的卖价挺高呢
It serves you right. Calamity Mine Healer was left behind by the companion. You're alone now.
活该 灾厄地雷僧侣被同伴丢下 孤伶伶的一个人了
Mr. Alvin will come and save me.
埃尔文先生一定会来救我
Because he's a person who can't see the atmosphere.
因为他是个不会看气氛的人
Give it back to me!
还我
That's the medical expenses you kicked me.
这就当作你把我踢飞的医药费
-Give it back! Give it back! You fugitive! -Just stay here.
-还我 还我 逃犯 -乖乖待在这吧
Is that something important?
那是很重要的东西吗
"SHOCKED" There's no such thing. Shocked.
(惊) 没这回事 惊惊
That's not the prize for the first dungeon challenge. Shocked.
那绝不是首次攻略迷宫后 得到的奖品 惊惊
SHOCKED
(惊)
What an understandable way of panic.
真好懂的慌张方式
Is your adventurer companion really all right?
你的冒险家伙伴 真的没问题吗
Mr. Alvin...
埃尔文先生…
I see. Carla was caught voluntarily.
这样啊 卡菈是自愿被抓的
Elder sister...
大姐…
Sorry, I'm not strong enough.
抱歉我的力量不够
You've tried your best.
你已经很努力了
I want to save her right away.
我很想立刻去救她
But you can't use the imperial body smoothly...
但无法顺利使用御神体…
Is there any other good way?
有没有什么其他好办法
How far is it from here to the castle?
这里离城堡多远
About two kilometers.
两公里左右吧
The curse that I'll die if I stay away from her hasn't started.
远离她就会死的诅咒没发动
Where's Altargaia?
奥尔特盖亚去哪了
Could he want to save Carla himself?
难道 他想自己去救卡菈
He disappeared without a word. It's like running away.
不吭声就消失 跟逃走没两样
I have no right to complain.
我没资格抱怨
Don't you run away?
你不逃吗
Wouldn't this party have been disbanded if there had been no curse?
不是说如果没有诅咒 早就解散这支队伍了
The party...
队伍啊…
That's right. Only now.
说的也是 只能趁现在了
All right. Let's run away.
好 逃走吧
We can't win if this thing doesn't come in handy.
这东西派不上用场的话 就不可能赢
How rude!
没礼貌
It talked!
说话了
Huh?
什么
My power will increase or decrease according to the moon.
我的力量会依照 月亮的阴晴圆缺而增减
Tonight is the new moon. My power will weaken.
今晚是新月 我的力量就会变弱
That's why Dolman chose to attack the dwarfs today.
所以多尔曼 才会选今天袭击矮人族
No wonder you couldn't exert power just now.
难怪刚才无法使出力量
But there's a way to retrieve my power.
但有个方法能取回力量
That's to let the healer cast magic on me.
那就是让僧侣对我施展魔法
The healer?
僧侣
If she casts recovery magic on me, I can use my maximum power.
只要她对我施展回复魔法 我就能发挥最大的力量
I'd like to ask a question.
我想问个问题
The curse on me was suddenly lifted.
在我身上的诅咒突然被解开了
Is it because of you?
是因为你的关系吗
Maybe.
有可能
You were naturally purified due to the holy power.
因神圣力量 自然而然被净化了
I see.
这样啊
Then I won't die even leaving Carla.
那我离开卡菈也不会死了
Is Carla the girl you were with?
卡菈 是刚才跟你在一起的女孩吗
Yes...
对…
Let me tell you something.
我告诉你一件事
You and that girl had a "deep" fate in your previous lives.
你跟那女孩前世有很"深"的缘分
What did you say?
你说什么
Half a century ago,
距今半个世纪前
you were lovers of the elves.
你们是精灵族的恋人
But your people were eliminated by the Dark Wizard army.
但族人被黑暗魔导士军团所灭
You swear to tie the knot when you're reincarnated.
你们发誓转世后定要结为连理
You've lost the memory of your previous lives. But you travelled together because of destiny.
现在 你们虽失去了前世的记忆 但因前世宿命而一起旅行
Carla and I...
我跟卡菈…
After defeating your old enemy, the Dark Wizard, your true love can be united.
打倒宿敌黑暗魔导士后 你们的真实之爱就能结合吧
True love?
真实之爱
Hold on. Half a century ago?
等等 半个世纪前
In terms of human age, Carla is still a kid,
卡菈以人类的岁数计算 虽然还是个小鬼
but she's been alive for 72 years.
但她已经活了72年
No, this is...
不 这是…
If they were reincarnations of lovers,
如果他们是相爱之人转世
they should've gotten along better.
感情应该要更好才对
You're right.
就是说啊
Oh, it really didn't work!
哎呀 果然没办法
I thought that would make you more motivated.
我以为这样说能让你更有动力
-So you tricked me. -Escapology.
-原来是骗我的 -逃脱术
Don't you run away!
别想逃
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
对不起 请原谅我
I'm the warrior in this party.
我是这支队伍里的战士
I'll do whatever I have to do.
该做的事我都会去做
Even if my level is 100 for the beginners
就算我的等级是初学者100等
and bracket laugh for adventurers level
冒险家等级括号笑
I'll never give up justice.
但我绝不会舍弃正义之心
You're... so weak.
你…这么弱哦
I shouldn't have said that.
早知道就不说了
It looks like nobody's guarding.
看样子没人看守
It's obviously weird.
明显很诡异
Listen.
听好了
Put me in the center of the enchanting magic array.
先把我放在封魔魔法阵中央
Holy power will remove the enchantment.
神圣力量会解除结界
So I can use magic in the cell.
这样 就能在牢房里使用魔法
What's wrong?
怎么了
Sorry, I don't have enough magic.
抱歉 我果然魔力不够
You can't be of use at all.
真的是派不上用场耶
What if we don't have Ryoko's sweeping items?
如果没有灵子的扫地道具怎么办
What a capable maid.
真是能干的女仆
More capable than you!
比你能干
Geez, Brigan already locked it.
可恶的布利迦 已经会上锁了
Ryoko, I'll leave it to you.
灵子 拜托你了
Okay.
好
Sorry to keep you waiting.
久等了
Did you call me? I'm here. I'm Carla.
叫我吗 我来了 我是卡菈
I'll complain about you later.
等等再吐槽你
Hurry and cast strong recovery magic on the crown.
快对王冠施展强力回复魔法
All right. Ryoko told me the whole story.
好 灵子跟我说了事情的始末
Let's start.
开始咯
Holy power, give the crown the power to resurrect.
神圣力量 给予王冠复活的力量
Add the power of thought.
追加念力
Evil thoughts?
邪念吗
There's no time to joke with you.
没时间跟你说笑了
I feel bad...
感觉好恶哦…
Imperial body, how is it?
御神体 如何
Thank you for trying hard. But the magic isn't enough.
感谢你的努力 但魔力不够
It still doesn't work.
还是不行
What?
什么
You showed me interesting scenes.
你们让我看到有趣的画面
Give up on struggling, Alvin.
埃尔文 放弃挣扎吧
They really found out.
果然被他们发现了
Ryoko, let's run away.
灵子 逃走吧
All right.
是
Miss Ryoko.
灵子小姐
Don't you run away!
别想逃
I'll teach you a lesson first, then take the crown.
先给你一点教训 再抢走王冠吧
What do you think, Mr. Alvin?
如何啊 埃尔文先生
Then I'll deal with the healer.
那我来对付僧侣
The maid who can't move is so boring.
不会动的女仆超无聊
Geez. What should we do?
可恶 怎么办
Run away now and come back at the full moon...
现在逃走 等到满月时再来也行…
Mr. Alvin.
埃尔文先生
Everything is over. Is this the end?
万事休矣 到此为止了吗
-Not yet. -Carla.
-还没 -卡菈
For the village head who knelt and kowtowed to me, I can't give them the imperial body.
为了跟我磕头下跪的村长 不能把御神体交给他们
I'll fight, too.
我也要战斗
Don't force yourself.
不要勉强
You'll be defeated.
你们会被打败的
Somebody...
来人啊…
Come and help us!
快来救救我们
Hi, sorry to keep you waiting.
嗨 让你们久等了
Is everyone all right?
大家没事吧
Altargaia!
奥尔特盖亚
Miss Anna.
安娜小姐
Even the golem is here.
连魔像都来了
The forest buddies are here, too. Roar.
森林伙伴们也来了吼
We'll fight together. Moo.
我们也一起战斗哞
Bad people are unforgivable.
坏人不可原谅
Beat them up.
揍爆他们
Especially the one who bullied Carla.
特别是欺负卡菈的家伙
Everyone...
各位…
Why are they all good people?
怎么都是好人
We have the advantage in quantity.
数量上是我们占优势
Come on!
上
Kuma!
熊
Moo!
哞
Bring it o...
随便你们葱辣…
All right. I knew what you were going to say. Look up.
好啦 已经知道你要说什么了 快抬起头来
Really? Don't I have to start over?
真的吗 我不用重新来吗
Take my secret medicine attack!
接受我的秘药攻击
Puff, I'll beat you all at once.
噗 看我一口气解决你们
Giant pig cyclone!
巨猪旋风
Puff...
噗…
What's wrong?
怎么了
I sprained my ankle.
脚扭到了
Here you go. Apply the bandage.
来 贴贴布吧
I won't let you in!
我不会让你们进去的
Everyone is still fighting outside.
大家还在外面战斗
Wait until it's over, then go out.
等到结束后再出去吧
-Grandpa. -Celia.
-爷爷 -希莉亚
I'm glad you're fine, Grandpa.
太好了爷爷没事
I've tried my best.
希莉很努力哦
You really tried your best.
你真的很努力
Celia.
希莉亚
The kid's pronunciation is not very accurate.
小孩子的发音不太准嘛
It's easy to deal with figures who can't avoid the eyes.
对付不会躲避眼神的人偶真轻松
Your magic is useless.
你的魔法一点用都没有
That's what you got me for letting me do it.
这是你让我出手的报应
My turn. It's my turn next.
换我 接下来换我
All you have to do is "ha".
你只要"喝"就好啦
I want to play, too.
我也要玩啦
Brigan, recovery magic.
布利昆 回复魔法
Brother Brigin, I'm coming.
布利基大哥 我马上来
You wish.
别想
Punish them as much as you like.
尽情惩罚他们
Call me queen.
叫我女王
Your opponent is me.
你们的对手是我
Wait a second.
慢着
Don't do this to them.
不准你对他们动手
Come on, sister.
姐姐 上啊
Protect Miss Maria!
保护玛莉亚小姐
Follow my orders, Undead Wolf.
听从我令 亡灵野狼
And me.
还有我
Miss Maria, thank you.
玛莉亚小姐谢谢你
It's gross yet lovely. It's a little contradictory.
恶心又亲人 有点矛盾
Well.
这样啊
Ellie, go back.
艾莉 快回去
Okay.
好
-Run. -Run. Run.
-快逃 -快逃快逃
Come on.
来啊
It serves you right. I'll bury you all.
活该 把你们全部埋了
Bury them all.
全部埋了
Open it. Open it.
快打开快打开
I'll scare you to death and level up.
我要吓死你们然后升级
Is there anybody open it?
谁快来打开啊
It's unexpectedly difficult to deal with.
意外的难缠
Right.
是啊
Carla, above you!
卡菈 上面
"MARIA" Good job.
(玛莉亚) 干得好
Amazing.
好厉害哦
Thank you. You saved us.
谢谢 得救了
But the demon soldiers keep coming out endlessly.
可是魔兵一直冒出来 没完没了
That's right. We have to block the source.
就是啊 必须阻断源头
Where's Alvin?
埃尔文呢
Everybody, look over there.
大家快看那
Mr. Alvin.
埃尔文先生
He rushed up alone, bear.
他一个人冲上去了贝尔
I think so.
好像是耶
Only Alvin has the item to fight Dolman.
因为只有埃尔文 有对抗多尔曼的道具
But my magic is too weak.
可是我的魔力太弱
I can't recover the imperial body.
无法让御神体恢复
Isn't that terrible?
那不是糟了吗
In that case...
这样的话…
When we run out of energy,
大家体力用尽时
we'll all die...
就会全灭…
Just adding magic will do, bear?
只要增加魔力就行了吗贝尔
It's too late, adventurer.
冒险家 太慢了
Geez, I failed.
可恶 失败了
Did you want to catch me off guard?
想来个出其不意吗
If you have the crown's power, you can fight with me.
若你有王冠的力量 就能顺利跟我战斗了
Shut up.
吵死了
Stop yelling, you outcast.
丧家之犬 别叫了
I'm invincible if there's no crown.
只要没有王冠 我就是无敌的
I can even get the whole world.
我甚至能得到整个世界
I'll eliminate your head with the crown.
把你的头连同王冠一起消灭
Mr. Alvin!
埃尔文先生
Carla!
卡菈
He was caught.
他被抓起来了
Holy power.
神圣力量
-The wand I gave you can enhance magic. -Give the crown the power to resurrect.
-我送你的魔杖 有增强魔力的效果 -给予王冠复活的力量
There's endless power.
力量源源不绝
Alvin, take off your helmet and just wear me.
埃尔文 拿下头盔直接戴着我
Got it.
知道了
Take this.
看我的
I'll beat you down.
我会打倒你的
You wish. I'll just cut off your head and take the crown.
别想 看我直接砍掉你的头 抢走王冠
My body is so light.
身体好轻盈
It's because of my support.
因为有我的辅助
-Amazing. -What a difference. Even his appearance.
-好厉害 -若判两人 连外表也是
Are they well-matched?
势均力敌吗
No, he's been suppressed.
不 被压制了
I'm here to support you.
我来支援
Mr. Alvin.
埃尔文先生
This is power enhancing magic.
这是增强能力魔法
That's...
那是…
I'll take that.
我收下了
What... has been enhanced...
增强了…什么啊…
It enhanced flavour and taste.
增强了风味和口感
Carla, you're amazing.
卡菈 你真厉害
I'm not surprised at all.
我一点都不讶异
-But well done. -Upside down. Upside down.
-但 做得好 -反了反了
Thank you, everybody!
各位 谢谢你们
Triplets?
三胞胎
I didn't expect Dolman is so old.
多尔曼年纪这么大哦
What a great achievement.
真是了不起的功绩
There should be stars next time the ranking is determined.
下次判定排行时 应该会出现星星了
I was just fighting with an old man.
我只是跟个老爷爷战斗而已
And there was support from the imperial body.
而且还有御神体的加持
I almost forgot it.
差点忘了
Give this back to me.
这个还我了
Sanko!
山靠
She's still looking well.
她还是这么有精神
You cherish that badge so much.
你这么珍惜那个徽章哦
It doesn't matter. Hurry back to the village.
不重要啦 快点回村子
You have to return the imperial body to the village head.
你得把御神体还给村长吧
How should I thank you?
我该怎么谢谢你们呢
I'd like to thank you.
我才要谢谢你们
My curse was lifted.
把我的诅咒解开了
That matter...
那件事啊…
Without me, the curse might start again.
没有我的话 诅咒可能会再次发动
Be careful.
小心点哦
How come?
怎么会这样
Mushroom, ghost, everybody, goodbye.
香菇 幽灵 各位 再见咯
Take care.
保重哦
Let's play together next time.
我们下次再一起玩
-I have to stay with Carla again. -Okay. I'll be waiting for you.
-又要继续跟卡菈在一起 -好 等你们哦
But I've been a one-person party for a long time.
不过 长久以来 我一直都是一人队伍
Such a big party was formed unknowingly.
不知不觉中组了这么大的队伍
All the members have strong personalities.
虽然成员都很有个性
But I wouldn't be able to fight Dolman without them.
但如果没有他们 我就不能跟多尔曼战斗了
Is it thanks to Carla...
这都多亏有卡菈吗…
What's the matter? Why are you staring at my face?
怎么了 为何盯着我的脸看
Nothing...
没有…
Have you fallen for me again because of the battle?
难道 因为这次的战斗 你重新迷恋上我了
It seems that my charm is irresistible indeed.
看来我的魅力果然无法档啊
What are you talking about?
说什么鬼话
I appreciate your sentiment.
我很感谢你的心意
Well.
就说了
But I think...
但我觉得…
It's too pathetic.
真是太可悲了
Pathetic.
口悲
You're so annoying.
烦死了
This healer is really annoying!
这个僧侣真的是烦死人了